// creating an array and passing the number, questions4, options,and answers
let questions4 = [
    {
        numb:1,
        question:"Choose the correct ecpression of approval?",
        answer: "Super",
        options:[
            "Rotten!",
            "Damn!",
            "Super",
            "Hell!"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb:2,
        question:"Which of the following is a Noun? ",
        answer: "Carelessness",
        options:[
            "Careless",
            "Caring",
            "Carelessly",
            "Carelessness"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb:3,
        question:"pick the word similar in meaning : AllEVIATE",
        answer: "Lessen",
        options:[
            "Lessen",
            "Clear",
            "Match",
            "Incite"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb:4,
        question:"Pick the word opposite in meaning:ABSURD",
        answer: "Sensible",
        options:[
            "Cruel",
            "Calm",
            "Sensible",
            "Sturdy"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb:5,
        question:"To Vouch for means",
        answer: "To confirm",
        options:[
            "To confirm",
            "To degrade",
            "To follow",
            "To supersede"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb:6,
        question:"I don't think I've ever......on that sofa",
        answer: "sat",
        options:[
            "sit",
            "sat",
            "been sitting",
            "sitting"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb:7,
        question:"Name the letter that is sent along with the cv (Curriculum Vitae).",
        answer: "Covering letter",
        options:[
            "formal letter",
            "Introductory letter",
            "Covering letter",
            "Business letter"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb:8,
        question:"Choose the corract sentence of the following",
        answer: "I prefer coffee to tea.",
        options:[
            "I prefer coffee by tea",
            "I prefer coffee for tea",
            "I prefer coffee than tea",
            "I prefer coffee to tea."

        ]
    },


    {
        numb:9,
        question:"To hold your horses means",
        answer: "To be patient",
        options:[
            "To be ready",
            "To be patient",
            "To be eager",
            "To be impatient"

        ]
    },

    {
        numb:10,
        question:"What is the antonym of Manly",
        answer: "Effeminate",
        options:[
            "Strong",
            "Feminate",
            "Masculine",
            "Effeminate"

        ]
    }
    
]
